If you go down to the woods today.
Mother's Day is a action, horror, comedy film directed by Charles Kaufman.
Three girls discover that two men are willing to do anything to impress Mother and what
impresses Mother is watching her sons commit acts of rape and murder.
Now these women are prisoners and lowered to pawns in the game of checkers between two dim wits
and their Maniac Mommy and the question becomes, can any of them escape, alive?
Abbey, played by Nancy Hendrickson.
Jackie, played by Deborah Luce.
Trina, played by Tiana Pierce.
Ike, played by Frederick Coffin.
Addley, played by Michael McCleery.
Mother, played by Beatrice Pons.
Mother's Day is a 1980 American rape and revenge slasher film directed, co-written and produced by Charles Kaufman,
brother of Troma Entertainment co-founder Lloyd Kaufman (who acted as an associate producer of the film).
The plot focuses on three women on a camping excursion who fall victim to
two deranged, murderous young men and their unhinged mother.
The film contains elements of the satire, thriller and slasher genres.
Upon its release, Mother's Day received criticism for its depiction of violence and rape, and
was banned in the United Kingdom by the British Board of Film Classification.
While not a success during its release and receiving a negative reception
from critics, the film has since developed a cult following.
It has also been subject to critical analysis from film scholars for its subtextual
commentary on consumerism and the proliferation of television in popular culture.
A loose remake of the same name was released in 2010.
The film explores themes of rape, revenge, murder, shocking, aggressive.
The tone is lighthearted and dark.